It's been leaking oil from coast to
coast for 3 years.
>> Please, sweet baby Jesus.
>> I feel like you guys are eternally
bonded now.
>> This has been fun.
>> [laughter]
>> Bleed over it.
>> I dropped the steering linkage on my
head. We took the alternator out three
times.
>> What all we put in this thing?
>> I pulled up to George's house and I
[music] wasn't sure he was going to be
able to do this.
>> The motor mount, timing chain, timing
cover gaskets.
>> Except for that 2 by 4 scaffold right
here.
>> Oil pan gasket, oil change, front crank
seal.
>> We got to do brake lines.
>> I was like, yeah, right. I had no
problem.
And we diverted a thunderstorm.
>> And we diverted it.
>> There was a thunderstorm coming in.
>> Yeah? You diverted it?
>> Uh well, I went, "God damn it's going to
rain."
>> And it didn't [music] rain.
>> It really did. And the sun came out like
right after we
>> And then he started taking parts off and
entire front end of his motor was laying
on this tarp last night.
>> to start it.
>> What'd you say?
>> Let me hear it. That's where we're at.
>> And we went in there and played poker
and shared a bottle of wine with his
family. It was a fantastic time, dude.
>> Please, sweet baby Jesus.
>> What? There's no clanking.
>> There's no knocking, dude. I swear to
God, we took so many parts off, we'll
never get them back on.
>> That's what happens when you know what
you're doing.
>> And that's why it never happens when I
do it. We came back out here and slammed
it and the first time we touched the
key, it crawled right up.
Hold on. Hold on.
>> I got to make sure it ain't leaking.
>> It's not leaking.
>> You don't even bother looking.
>> We used enough RTV, that ain't
going to leak for 20 years.
>> George is not a mechanic, he's a
magician. And this is the most love this
van has ever got.
>> It's been leaking oil from coast to
coast for 3 years.
>> And it's finally stopped.
>> Timing chain gasket.
>> I'll get by with a little help from my
friends.